Elizabeth Ispravnikava

3D - Graphic Designer

- Ptichka1995ab@gmail.com
- +48 573 481 561
- Poland, Gdansk Pomorskie

About

I'm a 3D and Graphic designer based in Poland. I have extensive experience in various fields of design. Such as graphic design, 3D modeling and UI / UX design. Working as designer since 2017. I am proficient in such graphic programs as Adobe Photoshop, Adobe illustrator, Adobe Indesign, Adobe After Effects, Corel Draw and a program for creating 3D models and images - Autodesk 3Ds Max and ZBrush. I also have a high level of knowledge of Figma and Sketch.

I constantly get new knowledge and skills, and do not stop improving. I get most of the knowledge in online courses - it's very convenient and saves a lot of time, which is of great importance in the modern world;)

Nothing is impossible for me, I can study any information and apply it in my work.

Education

Belarusian State University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Design

Expertise

Graphic design / Visual story-telling / Social Media Marketing / 3D modeling / 3D rendering / Digital design / Marketing Strategy / Branding / Product Promotion / **UX-UI** Design



Work Experience

Chief Marketing officer

2022 - Present

- Communication with all members of the design team, as well as with developers, architects, testers, managers
- · distribution and delegation of tasks
- working closely with product managers
- planning and optimization of the processes of the design development team

Team Lead Graphic Designer 2020 - 2021 **BKT-consult**

- development of user interface design
- development of specifications (description of reactions, visualizations)
- planning and optimization of the processes of the design development team

Graphic Designer

2019 - 2020

AMZ Supply

- Creation of corporate labels
- development of logos
- · corporate packaging and labels
- Creation of photographs for printing and posting on the site, processing and recreation of goods

Marketing Designer

2019 - 2020

LTD «UNAKI»

- · Creation of a trade mark and corporate identity
- Creation of packaging design, brochures, advertising
- Promotion and maintenance of accounts on social networks
- Creation of packaging design, brochures, advertising